http://www.cazarin.com/privacy-policy/

Certifications & Awards
Why Hire A Marketing Team?
Shopify Web Design
eLearning Distance Teaching – RTAPeLearning, Distance Teaching, Video teaching
Certifications & Awards
Why Hire A Marketing Team?
Your Privacy is important to us.Who We Are
Our company website address is https://www.cazarin.com/.
This policy also covers all subdomain sites under the domain cazarin.com.
What Information Do We Collect?
We collect information from you when you fill out a form.
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, phone number or company. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
What Do We Use Your Information For?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
1) To improve customer service
(Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.)
2) To send periodic emails
The email address you provide for order processing may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.
Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.
How Do We Protect Your Information?
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.
Do We Use Cookies?
We do not use cookies.
Do We Disclose Any Information to Outside Parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
In compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.
Online Privacy Policy Only
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our website’s privacy policy.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.
Cazarin Interactive
7064 East Fish Lake Road
Maple Grove, MN 55311
Send us an email
Schedule a Meeting
Let’s TalkTell Us About Your Project
Project Inquiry
7064 E Fish Lake Road
Privacy Policy | Sitemap | Client Forms
Required 'Candidate' login to applying this job.
Click here to logout
And try again
Login to your account
Username/Email Address:
Password:
Forgot Password? |
Sign Up
Save Password
Reset Password
Username/Email Address:
Already have an account? Login
Enter the username or e-mail you used in your profile. A password reset link will be sent to you by email.
Signup to your Account
First Name *
Last Name *
Username *
Email Address *
Password *
Confirm Password *
Phone:
Organization Name *
Select Sector:
Select Sector
Adobe Creative Suite
Adobe Experience Manager
Animation
Application design and project developers
Brand development
Content management
Copywriting
LOOKING
FOR LEADS?
Digital marketing is not magic—it is hard work. But there are actionable steps that you can take to maximize your online presence and build a website that converts. Learn how with our complimentary guide 7 Steps to Digital Marketing Success.
Email*
Answers
Job Alerts
Save Jobs Alert
Account Activation
Before you can login, you must active your account with the code sent to your email address.
If you did not receive this email, please check your junk/spam folder.
Click here to resend the activation email.
If you entered an incorrect email address, you will need to re-register with the correct email address.
Your Email:
Activation Code:
